

# ZHANG JING



+852 67419352/+86 13691907245



zhangjing2023good@163.com



HONG KONG/SHEN ZHEN

## **ABOUT ME**

Master of Science degree in AI & digital media

1-3 years of experience in branded social media management, KOL marketing, B2B sales

Strong passion for Web3, cryptocurrencies and blockchain

Excellent negotiation and relationship building skills Ability to work in a fast-paced startup environment

Excellent team player with an open mindset

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### 2023.02-2023.07 SOCIAL MEDIA OPERATOR/SALES

BOBOBIRD

GONG

- SHEN ZHEN-GUANG Help its watch brand establish an IG/TIKTOK account: bobobird\_factory
  - Publish over 200 original graphic and text content.
  - · Live streaming introduction products on the IG social platform
  - Formulate brand digital development strategy, liaise with KOL to complete product promotion

# HENG TONG GROUP

# • 2022.02-2022.07 TRAINEE ACCOUNT MANAGER

SU ZHOU-JIANG SU • Joined the company's PEACE transnational submarine cable project as a sales assistant. Help PEACE promote the signing of a US\$70 million order.

#### **EDUCATION**

• 2023-2024 **HONG KONG** 

# HONG KONG BAPTIST UNIVERSITY

• Master of Science in Al & Digital Media

• 2018-2022

SU CHOW UNIVERSITY

SU CHOW-JIANG SU

· Bachelor of Advertising

# LANGUAGE ABILITY

Mandarin **■**100% Cantonese 80% English 70%

#### **EXPERTISE**

- Strong analytical skills (Tableau/google analytics/Excel)
- Strong computer programming skills (python, database management)
- Strong personal drive (personal campus entrepreneurial experience)
- Fintech platform (Bloomberg) learning experience
- Cryptocurrencies trading experience